are you uh coming for the whole thing,
but especially to be coming to the
Saints,
>> man. More than thankful. More than
thankful for the opportunity and man, I
just can't can't wait to go down there
and put in some work with my boys, man.
You know, ain't too far from Baton
Rouge, man. I'm just an hour, so you
know, let's do it, man. Can't wait.
Can't wait.
>> How much contact did you have with the
Saints leading up to this? How much how
much did you know they had an interest
in you,
>> man? And I feel like with all the
coaches and gyms, man, I built a great
relationship and I kind of always had it
in the back of my head that I was going
there. This is the only hat that my
parents bought today, which is crazy.
And um, man, just love the facility and
just love the connections that I made
with them boys. And man, I just came
ready to go to work, man.
>> More than thank more than proud, man.
>> Was was the hat decision one because you
felt like that was a team you were going
to or was that your parents trying to
will it into existence? Man, honestly, I
I asked them if they can get all 32 hats
and my mom said that they only had the
Saints at the store they was at. So, you
know, we got the Saints. But hey, man,
dream come true right now.
>> Right now.
>> Where are you right now?
>> I'm I'm in Nashville in my backyard,
man. The the house is too crazy right
now. So, had to come outside, get some
air, breathe a little bit, and be
thankful. Thank God, man. Let's go.
Hey Baron, people think of you as a fast
guy, but you're more Tell us why you are
a good wide receiver.
>> Because I can do anything you want me to
do, coach. If you want me to go in there
and block, I'll go in there and block,
get a screen pass, let's do it. I'll run
through somebody, burning somebody. Just
whatever you need to do as a receiver,
man, I'm here to do it. And I'm doing it
with a smile on my face. Um, you know, a
great teammate at the end of the day and
just a guy that's always going to bring
the energy and the vibes to practice and
games, man. Let's do it.
Barry, were you a big fan of Rasheed
Shahid and those shoes you'd like to
fill?
>> Man, of course, man. He's a great great
return and you know, man, just looking
to, you know, do what I need to do, man.
Let's
>> Sorry, y'all. I'm sorry.
>> Barry, are you a little surprised that
Garrett Gus hasn't heard his name called
yet,
>> man? Man, yeah. But
man, man, we just trusting God and man,
Greg is a great guy, great quarterback,
and um you know, God God going to have a
time for him and man, when it h when it
when it come, I'm going to be man just
excited, man. Let's do it. Let's do it.
>> Have you have you spent time thinking
about okay, the the kick return at the
NFL level is a little different and how
>> right
>> handle that? How that you would approach
that your game?
>> Man, honestly, I like any any special
teams is a will to do it, man. And if
you want to do it, you'll get get out
there and do it. So man, there's nothing
to me. This something I've been doing,
catching the ball, taking it to the
house for 100 yards and celebrating with
my with my teammates, man. So I feel
like it ain't the difference with me.
It's just a will to doing and I want to
do it and I want to do it. So it's going
to get done.
>> What uh what makes for a good what makes
for a good returner,
>> man? Explosiveness and and honestly
fearless. That that's the biggest one
for me. Fearless. Being able to run
through the smoke and, you know, keep
your head up ch high and you know,
whatever comes with it, man. Just just
take it take it to the chin. Let's do
it.
Barry, you played uh in the senior bowl.
What was that like? And also, there were
a lot of Saints assistant coaches there.
Is that when you started saying that
maybe it could be the Saints?
Man, it was just a great experience all
around just going going down there and
getting some work in with the coaches
and just hearing hearing their point of
view of things and you know trying to
add my my point of view and you know we
working and just being coached up and um
just been being a lot of being around a
lot of great guys and you know competing
and that's something I like to do. I
compete my tail off. So you know just
being invited to one of the best of the
best you know doing my thing and you
know having fun while doing it. I always
say something about having fun cuz man
you just got to have fun with this stuff
man. So, um, man, Senior Bowl was a
blessing. Great experience, man. I'm
just ready, y'all. I'm sorry if I'm so
excited, man. I'm ready. Let's do it.
>> Barry, you talked at your pro day about,
you know, maybe the transfer didn't go
exactly how you had hoped and just going
through a season like that, just still
getting your name called. Just is that a
weight off your shoulders? What are the
emotions right now?
>> Um, yes, sir. And that's just a um
testimony that's man, it's going to be
sunlight and it's going to be dark days.
And regardless of how you may feel about
it, that's life and life. Life life's
going to keep going. So, um, just being
able to keep my best foot forward and
attacking each and every day like it's
my last and just out there having fun
and, you know, find enjoying it again,
man. I wouldn't I wouldn't I wouldn't do
it again for the world, bro. Love them
boys, man. Love them.
>> What do you think of all these offensive
weapons the Saints have come up with the
last few days,
>> man? Let's do it. I'm ready to work,
man. I'm ready to work. I'm ready to
work. I'm ready to work. Let's do it.
Come on.
Uh, Barry, when it comes to kind of
adding an element on offense for New
Orleans, what do you think about your
ability as a yards after your catch
receiver?
>> That's something that I've been doing
since a baby, man. It's just like I I
got a feel for the end zone and I always
looking to find an end zone. And that's
whether it could be a jet sweep, a deep
ball, a screen, slant, whatever the case
may be, man. I'm just looking to always
score the ball, man.
>> Hey, Baron, have you had a chance to
visit with Lane Kip and been down in
Baton Rouge since he's arrived?
Um, not really just visit with them, but
I didn't I didn't came and watched a few
practices and I was training and stuff
when I was down at NBR, but you know, I
just tried to stay out their way, you
know, let them keep getting better each
and every day. And, you know, I had some
something to do. I had a plan in mind in
my head. So, you know, I just had to
attack every day.